It's crazy. I still can't believe she vanished.
And it was right at midnight. The instant the date changed, Yuzuru was erased.
We've got to figure out which of these 12 Natsumi is impersonating.
Because it looks like if I don't, we run the risk of losing another person each night, one by one.
Yeah, that seems to be the case. The process of elimination will help.
Not much of a consolation when friends are vanishing, though.
I've got to find out who she is in a hurry. Not just for us, before Natsumi's sake too.
Well, in that case, isn't it about time for you to verify my identity? What if I'm her?
No way. You're the real deal. At least that's what I'm hoping is the case with all my heart.
What the hell does it matter what you want to believe? Your mission is to do what you can to verify it.
You could grill me with questions or, I mean, to judge my reaction or whatever.
You could, like, kiss me or something dumb like that.
I see. Then.
Well. Oh, okay.
Big brother, what are you doing? Give me those. Come on, they're mine. Give them that. No, thanks.
Oh, yeah. You're Coterie, all right.
Natsumi couldn't play this side of you so perfectly.
Isn't that right?
Coterie.
Oh, crap. I'm sorry.
I'm afraid.
I think we need to speed up the stating process.
I agree. I know we've already scheduled a pretty packed day, but I don't care. Let's fit as many more in as we possibly can before tonight.
I'll leave all the arrangements to you.
Understood. I'll do the best I can. As for right now, you're due to meet Miku. Better hurry.
I'm on it, thanks.
Thanks for coming, Miku. But, hey, why did you want us to wear costumes? It's kind of weird.
Oh, it's kind of an occupational hazard, I'm afraid. Being such a huge star means having to hide sometimes.
But I don't want you to worry. As you can see, we'll totally blend in if we cosplay here.
We're finally on a date by ourselves. I just didn't want anyone getting in the way of that.
Huh. That actually makes sense.
Whoa!
It's Kanon Tsukishima and Sieg from Valkyrie Misty!
And you're in the rarely cosplay mask from Episode 6 when they saved Misty!
Can we please take your picture?
Wait, what? Oh, no. I don't think we had...
Of course! We would be delighted!
Darling, your turn. Go on.
What? Me?
There it is! The signature pose of our beloved Sieg!
So, you gonna tell us why we're here or what?
Because FYI, if you're making amends, this isn't enough.
Oh, that's so lame, yo.
Oh, this has nothing to do with that day. Just thought we should hang. I mean, we're classmates, after all. I should know you better.
So, what is it that's troubling you, Shido? Why is it you're suddenly interested in talking about the future?
Uh, well, how do I put it? I guess I just feel like I need to start taking my life's path more seriously.
Oh, now I see.
In that case, do you remember the promise you made me?
Because I haven't forgotten it, Shido.
Hi-ya!
No way!
Ha-ha-ha! Did you see that? It was my signature move. You just witnessed the Dunkelhide win, Hosea.
Uh-huh.
Hmm. You'll never beat my crazy skills, Shido. Not now that I have this guy. With this legendary relic in my possession, you stand no chance of defeating me. So there!
Wait, how is it legendary? I mean, didn't you just buy it from that lady?
Well, if I were you, I would try to focus on my game. Don't forget, we promised that the loser of this match would do whatever the winner wants.
I'm well aware.
Get ready for a comeback!
And Shido's out, ladies and gents!
Come sit by me.
Yeah, okay.
My first order is, for the next ten minutes, you won't act surprised or flustered, nor will you try to stop me, no matter what. And you'll promise me to never speak of it again.
Right. Okay. I promise.
Thank you.
This is even more comfy than I thought it would be. Be good, and I'll turn you into my full-time pillow. How does that sound?
You've gotta be kidding me.
I'm sorry, are you complaining, my pet? Now then, I want you to rub my head very gently.
As you wish, master.
Hold on!
What the? What's wrong?
Yuzuru, I miss her.
Oh, Kaguya. Of course.
I know you said she was taking an exam, but really, you don't know where she is. I can tell. You think I'm stupid.
I would never.
But you thought it was better if I didn't know, right?
So I'll trust you. Because that fateful day, the one who gave me and Yuzuru a third choice, that was you, Shido.
Kaguya.
So I'm begging you, please, save Yuzuru.
Holy crap, you pathetic loser. Kidding. I meant the opposite of that. You beat the schedule and actually went on 11 different dates in two days. I'm exhausted thinking about it.
Well, can't complain. I'm the one who asked for it.
So? Did you sense anything wrong when you were talking to anyone?
No, nothing in particular. There's no doubt in my mind that Miku and Kaguya are real, and neither my teacher nor the girls seemed off to me.
This is hard. I know we need to figure it all out, but I dread knowing who Natsumi is.
Yeah. Sorry, bro. Unfortunately, I think it's time for you to give her an answer.
I know. Except, even if I wanted to make some kind of guess, how am I supposed to do that?
Hmm. We don't really know that either. This game seems guided by nothing but Natsumi's wins. She's holding all the cards.
I imagine even right now she's observing us from somewhere close by.
Right on the money!
You stay back!
Natsumi!
Ah! Good evening, Shido. Day two of the game is now at an end. Tell me something, are you having fun yet?
What is this even about, Natsumi? I never asked to play this game! Just bring Yuzuru back now and we can talk about anything you want!
Sorry, no chance. It's a bummer if you're not feeling up to the task, but the cork's kinda already out of the bottle, if you know what I mean. So, no time like the present, right? Why don't you give me your guess for today? Who am I impersonating?
I-I don't-
Shido, some won't be erased if you don't answer her. Even a wild guess'll do.
I think the one you're impersonating is Yoshino. I'm not confident in that, but she did seem unusually bold.
I see. Well...
Natsumi, wait!
She's gone! Do you think you were right?
Shin, Coterie, do you copy?
Reina? We're here. What's up?
Just now, Natsumi's angel showed up again. Two more people have disappeared. Both Aiyama Buki and Yoshino.
Two more days have passed, and I still haven't guessed correctly. Ms. Okamine, Mai Hazakura, me, Fujibakama, and Tonomachi have all been erased.
Shin, you're almost to the spot.
Sorry, did you wait long?
I just got here.
For the record, I've been observing her. She's been waiting there for over an hour.
Well, what are we seeing?
I don't know. I hadn't really decided.
So, in other words, you invited me not because you wanted to see a specific film, but instead because you wanted to spend some time with me.
Um, yeah. I mean, I guess. Sure.
How far are we going?
As far as you want.
Morikami?
Shido, I want you to touch me.
No brawl for easy access.
What? Here? You don't mean that.
That wore me out. Mind, body, and soul.
Shido!
Tolka! What are you doing out this late?
I wanted to check on you. These past few days, you've just seemed so preoccupied. I've been a little worried about you.
Sorry.
Oh no, you don't have to apologize. You're doing something important that you have to do. Isn't that right?
It's just, it's sad not being able to see you, that's all. If there's anything I can do to help, just say the word, okay?
Thank you. You're so sweet. I already feel like a whole new man.
Yay! That makes me happy.
Me too.
I'm so sorry to bother you. If I wanted to get to Tengu Street, would this be the right direction?
Yeah, that's right. Turn left at the second light and you'll run directly into it.
Thanks a lot. Broken GPS. I appreciate that you young lovers were willing to help me out.
What do you think? Did I sound awkward back there?
No, I highly doubt they suspect anything.
So that's Shido Itsuka, as well as the famous princess. They certainly don't seem any worse for wear.
Well then, good night Shido. Natsumi!
Yeah, good night Toka. Natsumi!
Natsumi. Or in other words, I love you.
Hey Coterie, I'm home.
Shido! There you are! Where the hell have you been?
I just heard from Reina a second ago.
She said it's Toka. Toka has vanished!
Please no, Toka! Toka! Toka!
Oh? Is it panic I hear in your sweet little voice?
Shido.
Natsumi!
Hey now, this isn't my fault. You're the one who didn't come home when you were supposed to.
I assumed you were forfeiting your guess tonight, so I did the thing and erase another person. You know how it goes.
You are the worst.
Still though, I'm kinda thinking I wanna end this pretty soon.
Wanna end what? What does that mean?
What it means is, if you guess correctly, I'll return all the people who have disappeared. Just know. If you don't guess right, then it's officially my win. And I'll take the place of every one of your missing friends from now on.
Those twelve precious friends of yours will unfortunately never be returning to this world ever again. Since this time is kinda special, I'll be back at 11.30 tonight.
Natsumi, wait! Natsumi!
I'll get it right. I'll save them. I will. All of them.
That's Shido. He makes the most adorable face whenever someone disappears. But that's not nearly enough for me. I want you to show me what true despair is!
That's the unlucky fate of those who see my dark secret. I'll watch you drown in your sorrow. And then nobody will be able to find me. Not that anybody looks for me anyway.
I want you to show me.
Yo! It's been quite a while. How long, Elliot?
Thirty years, give or take. You seem well, I. Good for you.
Okay, that's everyone, then.
Shido.
I know it's a lot, but at least now you understand what we're facing. I got you all involved in this. And I'm so sorry.
Look, don't worry about that. I just wish you'd told the truth. It really would have helped when Yuzuru disappeared.
This is embarrassing, but I think I'm the most sad to hear that our date was just a part of a research operation.
I have a long list of questions about this. But for now, I'll let it go and cooperate.
Thank you all. I mean it.
Okay, let's go through it all again. Natsumi is impersonating one of these twelve, and it could be anyone. These have been Shido's guesses so far.
Yoshino, Misokamine, and Maihazakura. I think we can exclude these three. In turn, Natsumi has erased. Yuzuru, Aiyama Buki, Hiroto Tonomachi, Miifuji Bakama, and Toka.
It's possible that she was actually one of those five. And then there are the five of us, of course. That makes us strong suspects. Although, to impersonate one of us might pose a little more of a challenge for her.
Huh? Wait, what do you mean by that? I get it. Our traits are too unique and complex, and that makes us hard to imitate, right?
Sure, yeah. Let's go with that.
This witch. The spirit you're calling Natsumi. Why would she take such a huge risk? The way she's handled it so far, every time a person disappears, it just increases our chances of guessing right.
So by the end, it'll be hard for us to lose. Which means the witch is confident we won't choose her. She knows that no matter what we might come at her with, it will never be the correct answer.
For example, she concealed herself inside a photo or something.
A good point. That is exactly the sort of creative thinking we need right now.
Don't you think maybe it's possible she isn't impersonating anybody at all? I really can't imagine that's the case.
Horikami is right. Why am I trusting Natsumi to play by the rules? She'd do anything to win. Which means she could even be one of these five.
What a party!
Natsumi!
She's the one!
Aw, she's so gorgeous, it's not fair!
Thanks for that. Now then, it's the night we've all been waiting for. What do you say? Do you think you can finally guess who I'm impersonating tonight, Cheeto?
Yeah, I'll get it all right. And you know what? It's for your sake too!
Eh, sure, give it your best shot. Now tonight is special because I'm gonna give you three guesses. You'll know right away if you're wrong, cause one of your friends here will disappear right before your eyes.
Isn't it exciting? Come on, Cheeto, give me the first name. Don't be Sean.
Okay. Well then for starters, I know you can't be one of the four people standing in this room. I can't imagine you'd bet everything on a game you had a 75% chance of losing.
So in other words, you're somewhere among the five people that you've erased. You made yourself safe as quickly as possible, as someone we'd least expect. And that is...
Yuzuru, the one who went first.
Shida, what are you saying? Yuzuru was the real deal. I am positive that she was my sister.
The thing is, I'm not certain about this either. At least, if Natsumi actually was Yuzuru, everything would make sense.
Oh, what a shame. You're so wrong.
You guys, she literally disappeared. You're kidding. It really wasn't Yuzuru? I've been saying that the whole time.
What's next, my darling little detectives? Who are you gonna name now? Don't take too much time, or I'll just have to suck someone else up.
Elliot is on the move, too. It's time to fill the vacancy in your support personnel.
The trick is, finding someone who's worthy of an adeptus number. Easier said than done.
Is it really, though? What about the one who gave you that scar? Now there's an outstanding wizard.
Damn it!
Keep it together, Shida. I think you're on the right track here.
Which one is Natsumi? Who is she?
I can't cope! I have no clue how it is!
We don't know enough to make a guess yet!
Sorry, gang, but time's almost up. I may just go ahead and vanish someone if I get tired of waiting.
Hold on! I think it's him!
Oh, too bad. Better luck next time!
Ah!
Kaguya!
Time for the grand finale, so this is your last chance. Who will you choose to be your final guess?
I can't take this, my darling! I can't!
To think I was lucky enough to finally meet Shida, and now I have to turn around and disappear!
Keep it together, Miku! You have to stay calm!
FYI, just 30 seconds left.
Darling, look at me. This is for you. I just can't bear to disappear without leaving a piece of me with you.
Miku!
Because if I wear this, then it'll only end up vanishing together with me!
Wear this...
Vanishing...
What? What are you thinking, Shida?
I've got it, Natsumi. I mean, I know the reason you're so confident.
While it's true that you're impersonating someone in one of the 12 pictures, it is not one of the people.
This was you. I know it!
You're Yoshinan!
No way! Why in the world would she...
Now that I think back, it was strange.
Yoshinan is Yoshino's puppet.
It shouldn't be able to see something that Yoshino can't.
What Miku just said made me realize.
When Yoshino disappeared, Yoshinan vanished right along with her.
Well then, I made my guess. You were impersonating Yoshinan, right?
You guys!
Toka!
Shida, where are we?
What happened to me?
So weird! I feel like I've been taking the longest nap ever!
Doubt. Why exactly am I here?
You're back! Yuzuru!
Oh, thank goodness. You all look okay.
Hey, Natsumi.
Care to explain why you did this? Because we're all listening.
Holy crap. Are you Natsumi?
Huh?
Ah?
Ah!
Anu, no!
Oh, I get it.
She has this filled out form only after she transforms using spirit power.
You saw! You saw, Damu! You saw everything!
You've now seen my secret not once but twice!
Twice! No! It is unforgivable!
And none of you are getting away with this!
I hope you enjoy this farewell present.
We'll meet again. Rest assured, I'll have my revenge!
Wait! Don't go! We can talk!
We can talk!
Shiro?
Huh?
They say there is only one truth.
However, the future can split into many different paths.
Which one will you choose?
Ahhhh!
Thank you.
Oh
You